Meng.
منغ.
Hang in there.
إصمد.
We'll go to the hospital right away.
سنذهب إلى المستشفى على الفور.
Right now.
الآن.
I got the patent.
لقد حصلت على براءة اختراع.
Let's go to the villa for my sister first.
دعنا نذهب إلى الفيلا الخاصة بأختي أولاً.
At a time like this,
في وقت كهذا،
why do you still care about her business?
لماذا لا تزال مهتما بأعمالها؟
If you won't take me,
إذا لم تأخذني،
I'll go by myself.
سأذهب بنفسي.
Fine.
بخير.
Whatever you say.
مهما قلت.
After we give her the stuff,
بعد أن نعطيها الأشياء،
we'll go straight to the hospital for a checkup, okay?
سنذهب مباشرة إلى المستشفى لإجراء فحص، حسنًا؟
Where's the stuff?
أين الأشياء؟
Finally got the upper hand.
أخيرا حصلت على اليد العليا.
Jiang Chunyu,
جيانغ تشونيو,
let's see how you can fight me now.
دعونا نرى كيف يمكنك محاربتي الآن.
Xiaomeng!
شياو مينغ!
Xiaomeng, what's wrong?
شياومينغ، ما الأمر؟
Xiaomeng,
شياو مينج،
what's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
What's wrong with Xiaomeng?
ما هو الخطأ مع شياومينغ؟
He just had a car accident.
لقد تعرض للتو لحادث سيارة.
Xiaomeng must have internal injuries.
لا بد أن يكون لدى شياومينغ إصابات داخلية.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Get him to the hospital now!
انقله إلى المستشفى الآن!
Sis.
أخت.
What you wanted,
ما أردته
I've given you.
لقد أعطيتك.
No!
لا!
Xiaomeng!
شياو مينغ!
Didn't you promise me
ألم تعدني؟
that you wouldn't leave me?
أنك لن تتركني؟
Didn't you promise your sister
ألم تعد أختك؟
that you'd protect me forever?
أنك ستحميني إلى الأبد؟
I can only accompany you this far.
لا أستطيع أن أرافقك إلا إلى هذا الحد.
Fangyue.
فانجيو.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
Xiaomeng.
شياو منغ.
Gu Nian.
قو نيان.
It's all your fault.
إنه خطؤك كله.
It's all your fault, you bitch.
إنه خطؤك كله، أيها العاهرة.
You not only killed my child.
لم تقتل طفلي فقط.
You also got Xiaomeng killed.
لقد تسببت في مقتل شياومينغ أيضًا.
Why wasn't it you who died?
لماذا لم تكن أنت من مات؟
You're the one who should die.
أنت من يجب أن يموت.
Why don't you just die?
لماذا لا تموت فقط؟
Go to hell.
اذهب إلى الجحيم.
Gu Xiaomeng.
قو شياو مينغ.
Didn't I tell you long ago
ألم أخبرك منذ زمن طويل
to leave this bitch sooner?
لمغادرة هذه العاهرة في وقت أقرب؟
But you wouldn't listen to me.
ولكنك لم تستمع لي.
You deserve it.
أنت تستحق ذلك.
Xiaomeng
شياو منغ
Now I'm the only one left.
الآن أنا الوحيد المتبقي.
Miss.
يفتقد.
The company called to say
اتصلت الشركة لتقول
today is the shareholders' meeting.
اليوم هو اجتماع المساهمين.
They're asking if
إنهم يسألون إذا
you plan to attend.
تخطط للحضور.
Tell them
أخبرهم
I'll be there on time.
سأكون هناك في الوقت المحدد.
Since we've come this far,
منذ أن وصلنا إلى هذا الحد،
no matter what,
مهما كان الأمر،
I will never admit defeat.
لن أعترف بالهزيمة أبدًا.
Are you sure you don't need me to accompany you?
هل أنت متأكد أنك لا تحتاج إلى مرافقتي؟
Gu Xiaomeng is dead.
مات قو شياو مينغ.
I'm afraid Gu Nian might become desperate.
أخشى أن يصبح Gu Nian يائسًا.
Really, there's no need.
في الحقيقة، ليست هناك حاجة لذلك.
Today is the final showdown between Gu Nian and me.
اليوم هو المواجهة النهائية بيني وبين قو نيان.
I want to face it alone.
أريد أن أواجه الأمر وحدي.
It's time.
لقد حان الوقت.
Shouldn't we start now?
ألا ينبغي لنا أن نبدأ الآن؟
10 minutes after the meeting starts,
بعد 10 دقائق من بدء الاجتماع،
if someone hasn't shown up,
إذا لم يظهر أحد،
they'll be considered to have forfeited their inheritance rights.
وسوف يعتبرون أنهم قد تنازلوا عن حقوقهم في الميراث.
Miss Gu is probably busy with funeral arrangements
ربما تكون السيدة جو مشغولة بترتيبات الجنازة
and won't be coming.
ولن يأتي.
Who says I'm not coming?
من قال أنني لن آتي؟
This contains the Mu family's patented core technology.
يحتوي هذا المنتج على التكنولوجيا الأساسية الحاصلة على براءة اختراع من عائلة Mu.
From today on,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
it belongs to our Gu Corporation.
فهو ملك لشركتنا Gu.
Miss Gu,
السيدة جو،
do you have the authorized transfer documents?
هل لديك وثائق النقل المعتمدة؟
If not,
إذا لم يكن كذلك،
this doesn't seem proper.
هذا لا يبدو مناسبا.
Indeed,
بالفعل،
this really isn't following protocol.
هذا لا يتوافق مع البروتوكول حقًا.
Yes, exactly.
نعم بالضبط.
This truly isn't proper procedure.
هذه ليست الإجراء الصحيح حقًا.
That's right,
هذا صحيح،
authorized transfer documents are mandatory.
مستندات النقل المعتمدة إلزامية.
When you worked with my grandfather
عندما عملت مع جدي
back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
were you this timid as well?
هل كنت خجولاً أيضاً؟
The agreed condition was to obtain the patent.
وكان الشرط المتفق عليه هو الحصول على براءة اختراع.
As for how we get there,
أما بالنسبة لكيفية الوصول إلى هناك،
it doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
Jiang Chunyu.
جيانغ تشونيو.
What are you laughing at?
على ماذا تضحك؟
Miss Gu truly lives up to her acting background.
إن السيدة جو ترقى حقًا إلى مستوى خبرتها في التمثيل.
Taking a stolen fake patent
أخذ براءة اختراع مزورة مسروقة
and daring to submit it to the board.
والجرأة على تقديمه إلى المجلس.
And still acting so righteous
وما زال يتصرف بهذه البر
that one can't help but admire your nerve.
لا يسعني إلا أن أعجب بشجاعتك.
What makes you say my patent is fake?
ما الذي يجعلك تقول أن براءة اختراعي مزورة؟
Because
لأن
the real one is with me.
الحقيقي هو معي.
But unlike you...
ولكن على عكسك...
I have Mu Qiushan's
لدي مو تشيوشان
personally signed authorization transfer document.
وثيقة نقل التفويض الموقعة شخصيًا.
It's completely legal.
إنه قانوني تماما.
Miss Gu,
السيدة جو،
you're not taking us shareholders seriously at all.
أنت لا تأخذنا، نحن المساهمين، على محمل الجد على الإطلاق.
So you and that bitch Fang Yue
إذن أنت وتلك العاهرة فانغ يوي
are working together.
يعملون معًا.
Miss Gu,
السيدة جو،
something terrible has happened!
لقد حدث شيئا فظيعا!
There are many police officers downstairs.
هناك العديد من ضباط الشرطة في الطابق السفلي.
They said there are several cases
قالوا أن هناك عدة حالات
that need your cooperation at the police station.
التي تحتاج إلى تعاونكم في مركز الشرطة.
[Police]
[شرطة]
Why panic?
لماذا الذعر؟
It's just an investigation.
إنه مجرد تحقيق.
I'll be back soon.
سأعود قريبا.
Wait.
انتظر.
To prevent Miss Gu from suddenly disappearing,
لمنع الآنسة جو من الاختفاء فجأة،
I'll have someone follow you,
سأطلب من شخص ما أن يتبعك،
and protect your safety at the same time.
وحماية سلامتك في نفس الوقت.
Wait a second.
انتظر ثانية.
I need to use the restroom.
أحتاج إلى استخدام الحمام.
Well...
حسنًا...
What?
ماذا؟
You're really treating me like a criminal.
أنت حقا تعاملني كمجرم.
Who knows who'll be running this company in the future.
من يدري من سيدير ​​هذه الشركة في المستقبل.
It's not decided yet.
لم يتم اتخاذ القرار بعد.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Where's Gu Nian?
أين قو نيان؟
She went to the restroom and hasn't come back yet.
ذهبت إلى الحمام ولم تعد بعد.
It's so cold today.
إنه بارد جداً اليوم.
I think it's going to snow heavily.
أعتقد أنه سوف يتساقط الثلج بكثافة.
When that happens,
عندما يحدث ذلك،
I want to build a snowman with Mr. Jiang.
أريد أن أبني رجل ثلج مع السيد جيانج.
How's it going?
كيف الحال؟
Any news?
أي أخبار؟
The nanny said it happened too suddenly.
وقالت المربية أن الأمر حدث فجأة.
She couldn't see who attacked them.
لم تتمكن من رؤية من هاجمهم.
Seems the kidnappers came prepared.
يبدو أن الخاطفين جاءوا مستعدين.
I suspect this
أنا أشك في هذا
has something to do with Gu Nian.
له علاقة بـ Gu Nian.
It was her after all.
لقد كانت هي بعد كل شيء.
I'll go stall her.
سأذهب لأوقفها.
You call the police.
اتصل بالشرطة.
No way.
مستحيل.
It's too dangerous for you to go alone.
من الخطر جدًا أن تذهب بمفردك.
Weiwei could be in danger at any moment.
قد يكون ويوي في خطر في أي لحظة.
We can't take that risk.
لا يمكننا تحمل هذه المخاطرة.
Besides, Gu Nian and I
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، أنا وGu Nian
need to settle things once and for all.
نحن بحاجة إلى تسوية الأمور مرة واحدة وإلى الأبد.
Stop it!
اوقفها!
Don't hit my mom!
لا تضرب أمي!
Mom!
أم!
Weiwei!
ويوي!
Jiang Chunyu.
جيانغ تشونيو.
You finally came.
لقد أتيت أخيرا.
Let Weiwei go.
دع ويوي يذهب.
If you have a problem, come at me.
إذا كانت لديك مشكلة، تعال إلي.
Fine.
بخير.
Jump from here.
القفز من هنا.
I'll release her immediately.
سأطلق سراحها على الفور.
Do you still think I'm stupid?
هل لازلت تعتقد أني غبي؟
Do you think I'd still believe you?
هل تعتقد أنني سأصدقك؟
If you don't jump,
إذا لم تقفز،
I'll kill her right away.
سأقتلها على الفور.
Fine.
بخير.
I promise you.
أعدك.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
Jump now!
اقفز الآن!
You always talk such a good game.
تتحدث دائمًا عن لعبة جيدة.
Why are you such a coward
لماذا أنت جبان هكذا؟
when death is staring you in the face?
عندما يكون الموت أمامك؟
Even if I die today,
حتى لو مت اليوم،
you won't escape.
لن تهرب.
The police are on their way.
الشرطة في طريقها.
Jiang Chunyu.
جيانغ تشونيو.
I came here today
لقد جئت هنا اليوم
with no intention of leaving alive.
بدون أي نية للمغادرة على قيد الحياة.
But you
ولكنك
must die before me.
يجب أن يموت قبلي.
Why are you so lucky?
لماذا انت محظوظة هكذا؟
Born with a silver spoon.
ولدت مع ملعقة فضية.
Having a loving family.
وجود عائلة محبة.
And Mu Qiushan who loves you so much.
ومو تشيوشان الذي يحبك كثيرًا.
But I
ولكن انا
have been living in the mud since childhood.
لقد كانوا يعيشون في الطين منذ الطفولة.
No matter how hard I try,
بغض النظر عن مدى جهدي،
there's always an invisible hand
هناك دائما يد خفية
pulling me back down.
تسحبني إلى الأسفل مرة أخرى.
Why is life so unfair?
لماذا الحياة غير عادلة؟
Don't blame everything
لا تلوم كل شيء
on fate.
عن القدر.
Everything that happened
كل ما حدث
is the consequence of your own actions.
هو نتيجة أفعالك الخاصة.
My mother,
والدتي
Old Mr. Gu,
السيد جو العجوز
they all died by your hand.
لقد ماتوا جميعا على يدك.
It's too late for words now.
لقد فات الأوان للكلمات الآن.
If ten years ago,
إذا كان قبل عشر سنوات،
when you first met me,
عندما قابلتني لأول مرة،
you hadn't harbored such evil thoughts,
لم تكن لديك مثل هذه الأفكار الشريرة،
perhaps things would have turned out differently.
ربما كانت الأمور قد سارت بشكل مختلف.
I have nowhere to go now.
ليس لدي مكان أذهب إليه الآن.
Jiang Chunyu.
جيانغ تشونيو.
Let's die together.
دعونا نموت معا.
Vivi, stay back!
فيفي، ابقي في الخلف!
Are you crazy?
هل انت مجنون؟
Chunyu.
تشونيو.
Qiushan.
كيوشان.
I've finally avenged my mother
لقد انتقمت لأمي أخيرا
and my grandfather.
وجدي.
It's all over now.
لقد انتهى كل شيء الآن.
We can go back to our normal lives.
يمكننا العودة إلى حياتنا الطبيعية.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Mr. Jiang.
السيد جيانغ.
Thank you and Mr. Mu
شكرا لك والسيد مو
for everything you've done for the children.
لكل ما فعلته من أجل الأطفال.
You're truly a loving couple.
أنتم حقا زوجين محبين.
It's what we should do.
هذا ما يجب علينا فعله.
Chunshan Children's Home
دار تشونشان للأطفال
is officially established.
تم تأسيسها رسميا.
That's wonderful!
هذا رائع!
So great!
رائع جداً!
Let's go in and take a look.
دعونا ندخل ونلقي نظرة.
Please, after you.
من فضلك بعدك.
Come.
يأتي.
Mu Qiushan.
مو كيوشان.
You're painting so enthusiastically by yourself.
أنت ترسم بمفردك بحماس شديد.
It seems that I, as your model,
يبدو أنني، كنموذجك،
am falling out of favor.
أنا أفقد تفضيلي.
Chunyu.
تشونيو.
Your every expression
كل تعبيراتك
is etched in my memory.
محفورة في ذاكرتي.
I could paint you for a lifetime.
أستطيع أن أرسمك مدى الحياة.